martinmadsen

software developer, me@martinbjeldbak.com

about

melbourne australia

29 years old +61 413 043 210 martinbjeldbak.com • / martinbjeldbak • / martinbjeldbak

languages

bilingual Danish/English IELTS score: 8.5

programming

Ruby on Rails Golang Heroku, AWS (EC2, RDS, ECS, S3), SQL GitHub Actions LATEX, HTML, Git JavaScript, Python OS X, Unix

interests

continuous delivery machine learning, devOps TDD, functional programming service oriented architecture web development

experience

since 2020 Software Engineer

ANZ Bank, Melbourne, Australia

Working on ANZ Plus as software engineer embedded in an integration services team. I am responsible for implementing & maintaining DevSecOps pipelines for feature engineers and developing microservices, mainly using GitHub Actions and Golang, respectively.

2016–2020 Lead Software Developer, Backend

NetEngine, Brisbane, Australia

Ruby on Rails software developer working with consultancy clients to build web-based systems across many different industries, from finance to flood mapping. I worked on setting up infrastructure in AWS to building GraphQL Rails APIs. I also partook in non-technical activities such as business planning, training new backend developers, etc. Clients included Apollo Motorhome Holidays.

2012–2014 Student Software Developer

Falck Healthcare a/s, Aalborg, Denmark

Development of Ruby on Rails-based system used daily by ca. 40 of Falck's physiotherapists to journal their patients' treatments and wellbeing.

education

2014–2016 M.Sc. in Computer Science

Aalborg University (AAU), Denmark

Majoring in Computer Science (120 ECTS) Specializing in Machine Intelligence

2014–2015 Studying abroad

University of California, San Diego (UCSD), USA

Fully accredited as part of the first year of my master's degree from Aalborg

University

2011–2014 B.Sc. in Computer Science

Aalborg University (AAU), Denmark

Majoring in Computer Science (180 ECTS)

projects

2015 **XQuery Processor**

University of California, San Diego, 0/

martinbjeldbak/xquery-processor

Implemented a subset of the XQuery and XPath XML query languages in

Java

2016 A Hierarchical Tree Distance Measure for Classification

martinbield-

bak.com/thesis.pdf

Concluded my M.Sc. degree. Published in Proceedings of the 6th International Conference on Pattern Recognition Applications and Methods - Volume

1: ICPRAM 2017, pages 502-509